Welcome to Scene Naps Studio. We're
solving a real problem in text-to-image
generation. Prompts are messy,
unstructured, and when the image doesn't
match what you pictured, you usually have
no idea what went wrong or what to change.
Scene Naps fixes this with a simple
two-phase pipeline. Phase 1 is prompt
enhancement. You start with a plain prompt
like, "A woman walking through a neon
city at night." Our DSPy pipeline breaks
that single sentence into four clear
parts, elements, meaning who or what is in
the scene, objects, meaning what they
look like and what's present, actions,
meaning what's happening, and
cinematography, meaning the camera angle,
lighting, composition, and mood. Each
composable element stays in its own lane,
so every detail is clearly labeled, easy
to edit, and never spills into the wrong
part of the prompt. Phase 2 is generation
and validation. We generate multiple
images using Nano Banana Pro.
Each result is scored by Joy Quality, a
fine-tuned SIGlib2 encoder model trained
on pairwise preference, which ranks both
aesthetic appeal and technical quality.
Then our VLM guardrails checks that the
image actually aligns with the prompt and
matches what you asked for. And here's the
best part. If you wanna change a
particular component, like make it golden
hour lighting, we only regenerate the
cinematography part. That makes
refinements fast, cheap, and predictable.
We also integrated Freepik semantic search
for reference images, and you can control
the entire workflow with your voice using
Gemini's live API. Scene Naps, composable
prompts, validated generations, and real
control over your creative vision. Thank
you.